# Suyeong Park

suyeong.park0@gmail.com — github.com/euphoria0-0

## RESEARCH INTEREST

My Research interests are mainly on making more **Trustworthy AI** using collaborations of information in data and knowledge from human-beings. I mainly focused on estimating uncertainty on Bayesian approach, especially 'what information we need between **representativity and uncertainty** for better ML model'. Currently, I believe 'understanding an intrinsic attributes of things using our knowledge' is crucial for deploying ML models for better human-being life in a real-world. Thus, I'm currently interested in identifying **CAUSALITY** of things from our data for explainable AI while overcoming the limitations of typical ML.

#### EDUCATION

## Ulsan National Institute of Science and Technology (UNIST)

Ulsan, Korea

Master of Science in Artificial Intelligence

Aug. 2020 - Aug. 2022

GPA: 4.15/4.3

Advisor: Prof. Kwang In Kim and Prof. Namhoon Lee

Thesis: Active Client Selection for Communication-efficient Federated Learning [Link]

Relevant Coursework: Causal Learning & Explainable AI, Reinforcement Learning, Advanced Machine Learning Topics

University of Seoul Seoul, Korea

Bachelor of Science in Statistics and Data Science

Mar. 2015 - Feb 2020

GPA: 3.7/4.5

Relevant Coursework: Bayesian Statistics, Machine Learning, Deep Learning, Time Series Analysis, Multivariate Statistics, Statistical Computing, Linear Algebra, Probability Theory, Mathematical Statistics

#### EXPERIENCE

# Visiting Researcher Jul. 2022 - Aug. 2022

CausalML Lab, Purdue University (supervised by Prof. Dr. Murat Kocaoglu)

West Lafayette, USA

• Research Project: Bayesian Causal Discovery

Research Assistant Aug. 2020 – Aug. 2022

Machine Learning and Vision Lab, UNIST (supervised by Prof. Dr. Kwang In Kim)

Ulsan, Korea

• Research Projects: active learning, transfer learning, federated learning, image attribute estimation

## Intern, Data Analyst and Engineer Mar

Mar. 2020 - Jun. 2020

Seoul Big Data Campus

Seoul, Korea

• Projects: Citizen Movement and Consumption Behaviour analysis around Seoul city

## Intern, Data Analyst Assistant

Sep. 2019 - Feb. 2020

FSC (Financial Services Commission)

Seoul, Korea

• Projects: Data analysis using financial public data

#### Publication

S. Park, Y. Ahn, K. Kim. Blind (keyword: Deep Active Learning, Bayesian) [Preprint] In Submission, 2022

S. Park, Active Client Selection for Communication-efficient Federated Learning [Link] Master's Thesis, 2022

## **PROJECTS**

#### Visual Common Sense Through Self-supervised Learning for Restoration of Invisible Parts in Image

April 2021 – Present

• Image Attribute Recognition

#### Causal Learning with Artificial Intelligence

Mar. 2021 – Dec. 2021

• Causal Discovery with genome data

## Citizen Movement and Consumption Behaviour analysis around Seoul city

Apr. 2020 – Jun. 2020

• Data analysis with card consumption, moving population data by Seoul city region Financial data analysis using financial public data

## • Data analysis with financial public dataset in Financial government

Jan. 2020 – Feb. 2020

## TECHNICAL SKILLS

Languages: Python, R, SQL (MySQL)

Frameworks: PyTorch, TensorFlow, Scipy, Matplotlib Developer Tools: Git, Docker, PyCharm, VSCode

Others: QGIS, Tableau, SAS

#### Talks and Teaching

## **Guest Talk**

## CSE362 Artificial Intelligence, Department of CSE, UNIST

Nov. 2021

Introduction to Federated Learning (for undergraduate students)

## Teaching Assistant

## AI519 Advanced Machine Learning Topics, AI Graduate School, UNIST

Fall. 2021

## Extra-curricular Experience

## Exchange Student

Jun. 2018 - Aug. 2018

Universidad San Ignacio De Loyola

Cusco, Peru

• Coursework: Spanish, Photograph

## **Exchange Student**

Aug. 2017 - Feb. 2018 The Haque, Netherlands

The Hague University of Applied Sciences

• Coursework: User Experience Design, Design Programming

Last Updated: November 15, 2022